<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thirty Days of Bible Verses 2</string>
    <string name="day_1_verse">Matthew 6:26 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_1_passage">Behold the fowls of the air: for they sow not, neither do they reap, nor gather into barns; yet your heavenly Father feedeth them. Are ye not much better than they?</string>
    <string name="day_2_verse">Job 13:15 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_2_passage">Though he slay me, yet will I trust in him: but I will maintain mine own ways before him.</string>
    <string name="day_3_verse">Psalm 23:1 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_3_passage">The Lord is my shepard; I shall not want.</string>
    <string name="day_4_verse">1 Chronicles 16:34 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_4_passage">O give thanks unto the Lord; for he is good; for his mercy endureth for ever.</string>
    <string name="day_5_verse">Proverbs 3:5 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_5_passage">Trust in the Lord with all thine heart; and lean not unto thine own understanding.</string>
    <string name="day_6_verse">Deuteronomy 31:6 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_6_passage">Be strong and of a good courage, fear not, nor be afraid of them: for the Lord thy God, he it is that doth go with thee; he will not fail thee, nor forsake thee.</string>
    <string name="day_7_verse">Matthew 6:33 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_7_passage">But seek ye first the kingdom of God, and his righteousness; and all these things shall be added unto you.</string>
    <string name="day_8_verse">John 3:16 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_8_passage">For God so loved the world, that he gave his only begotten Son, that whosoever believeth in him should not perish, but have everlasting life.</string>
    <string name="day_9_verse">John 14:1 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_9_passage">Let not your heart be troubled: ye believe in God, believe also in me.</string>
    <string name="day_10_verse">Matthew 7:7 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_10_passage">Ask, and it shall be given you; seek, and ye shall find; knock, and it shall be opened unto you.</string>
    <string name="day_11_verse">Job 5:17 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_11_passage">Behold, happy is the man whom God correcteth: therefore despise not thou the chastening of the Almighty.</string>
    <string name="day_12_verse">Revelation 3:20 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_12_passage">Behold, I stand at the door, and knock: if any man hear my voice, and open the door, I will come in to him, and will sup with him, and he with me.</string>
    <string name="day_13_verse">Psalm 51:10 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_13_passage">Create in me a clean heart, O God; and renew a right spirit within me.</string>
    <string name="day_14_verse">Psalm 19:1 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_14_passage">The heavens declare the glory of God; and the firmament sheweth his handywork.</string>
    <string name="day_15_verse">Job 42:5 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_15_passage">I have heard of thee by the hearing of the ear: but now mine eye seeth thee.</string>
    <string name="day_16_verse">Luke 1:37 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_16_passage">For with God nothing shall be impossible.</string>
    <string name="day_17_verse">Psalm 23:4 (NIV)</string>
    <string name="day_17_passage">Even though I walk through the darkest valley, I will fear no evil, for you are with me; your rod and your staff, they comfort me.</string>
    <string name="day_18_verse">Jeremiah 29:11 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_18_passage">For I know the thoughts that I think toward you, saith the Lord, thoughts of peace, and not of evil, to give you an expected end.</string>
    <string name="day_19_verse">Romans 8:28 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_19_passage">And we know that all things work together for good to them that love God, to them who are the called according to his purpose.</string>
    <string name="day_20_verse">Matthew 18:20 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_20_passage">For where two or three are gathered together in my name, there am I in the midst of them.</string>
    <string name="day_21_verse">Psalm 37:5 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_21_passage">Commit thy way unto the Lord; trust also in him; and he shall bring it to pass.</string>
    <string name="day_22_verse">Psalm 27:14 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_22_passage">Wait on the Lord: be of good courage, and he shall strengthen thine heart: wait, I say, on the Lord.</string>
    <string name="day_23_verse">1 Samuel 16:7 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_23_passage">But the Lord said unto Samuel, Look not on his countenance, or on the height of his stature; because I have refused him: for the Lord seeth not as man seeth; for man looketh on the outward appearance, but the Lord looketh on the heart.</string>
    <string name="day_24_verse">Romans 8:38-39 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_24_passage">For I am persuaded, that neither death, nor life, nor angels, nor principalities, nor powers, nor things present, nor things to come, Nor height, nor depth, nor any other creature, shall be able to separate us from the love of God, which is in Christ Jesus our Lord.</string>
    <string name="day_25_verse">Romans 6:23 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_25_passage">For the wages of sin is death; but the gift of God is eternal life through Jesus Christ our Lord.</string>
    <string name="day_26_verse">Ephesians 4:31-32 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_26_passage">Let all bitterness, and wrath, and anger, and clamour, and evil speaking, be put away from you, with all malice: And be ye kind one to another, tenderhearted, forgiving one another, even as God for Christ\'s sake hath forgiven you.</string>
    <string name="day_27_verse">Isaiah 40:31 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_27_passage">But they that wait upon the Lord shall renew their strength; they shall mount up with wings as eagles; they shall run, and not be weary; and they shall walk, and not faint.</string>
    <string name="day_28_verse">Ecclesiastes 12:13 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_28_passage">Let us hear the conclusion of the whole matter: Fear God, and keep his commandments: for this is the whole duty of man.</string>
    <string name="day_29_verse">John 1:1 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_29_passage">In the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God.</string>
    <string name="day_30_verse">Isaiah 53:4 (KJV)</string>
    <string name="day_30_passage">Surely he hath borne our griefs, and carried our sorrows: yet we did esteem him stricken, smitten of God, and afflicted.</string>
    <string name="day">Day %d</string>
</resources>
